guardian-angel-reading.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Padre, medium and online Reading of the Angels

_Last update: 12/09/2019_

Sesam Limited would like to thank you for visiting guardian-angel-reading.com (the “website”) and for your interest in our products and services. Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable while visiting our website. Sesam Limited recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of personal data collected. This document explains clearly and simply which of your personal data are collected by our website and how these personal data are used. You will also find essential information on your rights with regard to the sharing, transmission, alteration or deletion of your personal data. Please read this document carefully so that you fully understand our privacy policy. This privacy policy is subject to any applicable mandatory local laws and regulations.

By using the website, you acknowledge and agree to the application of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, do not proceed to further web pages of the guardian-angel-reading.com website.

## About guardian-angel-reading.com

The guardian-angel-reading.com website belongs to Sesam Ltd – Unit 3007, 30/F Tower 2, Metroplaza 223 Hing Fond Road, Kwai Chung, NT, Hong Kong – Business Registration #1930728 – VAT identification number: EU826411144, acting as the controller (hereinafter “Sesam Limited”, “we”, “us” or “our”). Depending on the means of payment chosen by the client, payments will be processed by Sesam Limited or its partner: Sesam Limited – 8A Pitmans Alley – Main Street – Gibraltar –  Business Registration #109779.

## What is to be considered when data is transferred over the internet?

The internet is generally not regarded as a completely secure environment, and information sent via the internet can be accessed by unauthorized third parties. Even if both sender and recipient are located in the same country, information sent via the internet may be transmitted across international borders and be forwarded to a country with a lower data protection level than the one existing in your country of residence. Please note that we accept no responsibility for the security of your information whilst in transit over the internet to guardian-angel-reading.com.

## What legal basis do we rely upon to process your personal data?

We may process your personal data on the basis of: (i) your consent, (ii) the necessity for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract and/or (iii) our legitimate interests (specifically, getting to know your preferences so as to enable us to personalize our offers and, ultimately, offer products and services that better meet your needs and desires and providing you with offers of products and services which you may be interested in), where applicable.

## What information is collected?

We do not collect your personal data through our website unless you voluntarily provided such data that could be used to identify a person. Through its website, guardian-angel-reading.com processes several categories of personal data.

In order to receive your free trial offer, we will collect and process – on the Free Trial Form you can access using this link – the following information: title, surname, first name, date and time of birth, e-mail address and country of residence. We rely in that respect upon the necessity for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract and our legitimate interests, as described above. There is no obligation to buy.

In order to answer your request communicated through the form on our contact page, we will collect and process the following information: subject matter of the question, e-mail address, surname, first name, content of the message and country of residence. We rely in that respect upon the necessity for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract and our legitimate interests, as described above.

If you decide to order a chargeable product or electronic service, you will then need to enter the following information: title, surname, first name, e-mail address, full address, telephone number, birthdate and method of payment/credit card details. Except for the credit card details (see further explanations in that respect in the next paragraph), we process the personal data listed above as well as a log of your purchase(s) of product(s) or electronic service(s). We rely in that respect upon the necessity for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract and our legitimate interests, as described above.

You enter your confidential credit card details within a secure area managed entirely by the payment processors or PCI DSS-compliant suppliers working with us. Sesam Limited does not have access to this entirely secure area under any circumstances.

When you visit guardian-angel-reading.com, our web server may also automatically collect your IP address. Furthermore, our web server may automatically collect generic information which does not identify you personally such as your web browser, your operating system or your Internet service provider.

We do not process your personal data for a longer period of time than necessary. If you do not use or purchase service(s) and/or products for twelve months, we will stop processing and erase your personal data, unless applicable law authorizes or requires personal data to be kept for a longer period.

Google reCAPTCHA  
We may use “Google reCAPTCHA” (hereinafter “reCAPTCHA”) on our websites. This service is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States (“Google”). reCAPTCHA is used to check whether the data entered on our website (for instance in a contact form) were entered by a computer or any other automated program. To that end, reCAPTCHA analyzes the visitor’s behavior taking several characteristics into consideration. This analysis starts as soon as the visitor connects to the website. reCAPTCHA will analyze several elements: the IP address, the period of time during which the site is visited or the cursor movements of the user). The data collected during the analysis will then be transmitted to Google. The analysis performed by reCAPTCHA take place in the background. Visitors of the website are not informed that such an analysis is underway. Data processing is based on the Article. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in protecting its site from abusive automated exploration and spam. For more information about Google reCAPTCHA and Google’s privacy policy, please follow the following links: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/> and <https://www.google.com/recaptcha/intro/android.html>

## How is this information used?

All the personal data and other information which we process are solely used in order to provide you with the service(s) and/or products which you requested on guardian-angel-reading.com and for the purposes of technical administration, research and development of the guardian-angel-reading.com website, customer and end user administration and marketing (hereinafter “Services” and “Products”). A secret algorithm based on your surname, first name and date of birth enables us to generate your free trial offer, as well as all the personalized psychic reading products which you can order.

Your e-mail address will also be used to send you the Products and Services which you ordered on guardian-angel-reading.com. We will also use your e-mail address to send you offers for Products or Services – every 2 to 3 days – which may be of interest to you, as authorized by law. You will also receive a free newsletter containing your horoscope and articles on subjects in the field of esotericism, clairvoyance or personal development. You can unsubscribe from this mailing list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link you can find in each e-mail we send you or on the contact page you can access via this link. We will then remove your contact information from the lists used for such mailings.

Your phone number will be used to send you offers for Products or Services that might interest you through text messages twice or three times a month. If you communicate your phone number, it means that you give Sesam Limited the authorization to send to this number text messages and phone calls recorded in advance, including promotional messages that could be sent through an automatic phone system composition. Receiving those messages or accepting receiving them doesn’t represent any obligation to buy. Please note that standard message rates and data charges from your cellular service provider apply to sending and/or receiving text messages or calls. You are solely responsible for such message rates and data charges. The costs linked to the aforesaid messages and data are only your responsibility. If you don’t want to receive more messages, you can ask us at any moment. (See “[How do I unsubscribe?](https://www.beta.guardian-angel-reading.com/legal-terms/#unsubscribe)” in our General Terms and Conditions of Use).

## In which cases will this information be disclosed?

Sesam Limited may disclose your information to its employees, agents and affiliates inside or outside your country of residence to perform Services for Sesam Limited. Our employees, agents, affiliates and third party providers who have access to personal data obtained through the guardian-angel-reading.com website are obliged to respect privacy.

We may transfer your personal data to third parties, processors and partners, who act for us for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. For example, sometimes a third party may have access to your personal data in order to fulfil an order, support our information technology or help compile and manage the data.

When transferring personal data internationally we make sure that we comply with applicable laws and regulations and take steps to make sure that the recipients of your information maintain an adequate level of data protection, including through the EU Commission standard contractual clauses. We also transfer data to the USA for hosting purposes to companies subject to the US-EU Privacy Shield.

Sesam Limited reserves the right to disclose your personal data in the event of a summons to appear in court, an official court order or any legal process or investigation in order to establish or exercise your rights, or to defend ourselves against claims permitted by the applicable laws and regulations. Your personal data may also be disclosed if Sesam Limited decides that it is necessary to hold an enquiry or take measures regarding potentially illegal activities in the event of threat to the personal security of any individual, or if you are in breach of the Service’s and/or Product’s General Terms and Conditions of Use.

## How do we share your personal data?

Only if you have accepted to receive offers in the field of clairvoyance from Padre’s partners (by ticking the specific consent box) could we share your personal data such as title, first name, surname, postal address and e-mail address with the relevant third-party company(ies), partner(s) of Sesam Limited, whose products or services may be of interest to you. These third-party companies may then send you offers too. To the extent permitted by the applicable local laws and regulations we reserve the right to share your personal data with third parties who assist us in providing Services to you, if they provide an adequate level of data protection to ensure the security of your personal data. However, you can contact us at any time through the contact page you can access via this link in order to ask us not to disclose your personal data to third parties.

Sesam Limited’s suppliers sometimes have temporary and limited access to your personal data. This access may be granted in the context of maintenance operations or the supply of Services to Sesam Limited. In particular, these suppliers offer services in the following areas: payment processing, e-mail routing, SMS routing, mail printing and sorting, website hosting, after-sales service processing, data storage, as well as any other service linked to the operation, maintenance and security of Sesam Limited’s website. However, access to your personal data remains strictly limited to what is required by the supplier in order to fulfil its service contract with Sesam Limited. Moreover, such access is strictly limited to the time required for the operation or service.

Sesam Limited ensures contractually that its suppliers undertake to do everything within their power to ensure the protection and privacy of your personal data according to the principles defined in this document and applicable law. These suppliers are also required not to use or transfer your personal data for purposes other than those defined in the service contract taken out by Sesam Limited.

Sesam Limited strives to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of your personal data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases and the data we collect. Sesam Limited ensures the security of all your personal data, using technical and organizational security measures to reasonably protect information against unauthorized access, accidental or intentional manipulation, misuse, loss and destruction, as well as a processing procedure which complies with the applicable legislation.

## How can I exercise my rights in relation to my personal data?

You have the right to access your personal data, as collected and processed by Sesam Limited, and to request that they be corrected in the event of inaccuracy (if any) or deleted in the event that they are not necessary. You have the right to ask for a restriction of processing or to object to processing as well as the right to data portability. You also have the right to object to the future processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes at any time, without charge and without justification.

To exercise your rights, all you need to do is to contact us at [privacy@guardian-angel-reading.com](mailto:privacy@guardian-angel-reading.com)

In general, you also have the right to withdraw your consent to any processing based on your consent (if any) at any time. This withdrawal of consent does not compromise the legality of the processing based on consent made prior to such withdrawal. If you consider that the processing of your personal data constitutes a violation of the data protection law(s), you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of the European Union of your usual place of residence, your place of work or the place where the violation occurred.

In order to protect your privacy and the security of the data recorded on our website, we may ask you for additional information in order to check your identity before we answer your query.

## What other information is collected, used and disclosed?

We also collect your non-personal data which are used in order to optimize the published website and its content in order to offer you a personalized browsing experience. This information is used to analyze the performance of the website and the way in which it is used by Internet users. This information is also used to offer you products, programs or Services. It may also be disclosed to and/or shared with third parties if it does not contain personal data.

## Who else can collect information via our website?

guardian-angel-reading.com’s website may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy is not applicable to any internet websites controlled by third parties not affiliated with Sesam Limited that the guardian-angel-reading.com website may link to (“Third Party Sites”). Please review the privacy policies of Third Party Sites as Sesam Limited is not responsible for and has no influence on the content or the privacy practices of Third Party Sites.

## Use of cookies, IP addresses and website traffic information

Sesam Limited uses tracking technology such as cookies or tags to gather such information as outlined above (see “What information is collected” and “How do we share your personal data“) and to understand how visitors use the guardian-angel-reading.com website. Tracking technology helps us manage and improve the usability of the guardian-angel-reading.com website, for example by determining whether there has been any contact between your computer’s IP address and us in the past and identifying the most popular sections of the guardian-angel-reading.com website. In concrete terms, guardian-angel-reading.com’s server sends information to your computer, mobile phone or other electronic device which is then stored on your hard drive. The IP address of your computer or other device is used in order to identify visits to guardian-angel-reading.com from your computer or other device and to keep track of your browsing habits and optimize the time required to load pages.

Cookies are pieces of data (small electronic text files) stored on your device/terminal equipment that contain data about a user or its device. They allow the storage of information for a determinate period of time and the identification of the user’s electronic device.

When you visit the website for the first time, the entry page will show information on privacy and respective wording regarding the consent to the use of cookies through a _“cookie banner”_. If you continue to actively use the website and do not actively object to the use of cookies, you agree to our use of cookies and your IP address and such consent will be stored in your browser, so that the information does not have to be repeated on every page of the website. Should the consent be missing in your browser (e.g. if you deleted your browser history), the _“cookie banner”_ with privacy information will appear again the next time you visit the website.

In order to render the services, we install and use certain technically required cookies which therefore do not require your prior consent. We also use session cookies which are automatically deleted at the end of your session and which also do not require your prior consent. Other cookies (such as cookies to improve the navigational experience by keeping record of certain data – this avoids you having to reintroduce such data at each connection – and by tailoring the content of the services to your preferences) may be installed and used on the basis of your consent. You may, at any time, delete or block cookies in your browser parameters or through Ads settings and Ads settings for mobile apps. However, in such case some functionalities of the services or website requiring the use of cookies for technical purposes may be reduced or may no longer be available to you.

We use analytics cookies to gather general information on how users use the services and the website, e.g. which pages they visit most frequently and whether they receive any error messages from websites. These cookies do not collect any data that may lead to an identification of the user. All information collected with the aid of such cookies exclusively serves the purpose to comprehend and improve the functionality of our services and website. We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). The information regarding your usage of the services and the website generated by the use of Google Analytics is usually transmitted to and stored on a Google server in the US. Google will use this information on our behalf to analyze your use of the website, compile reports on website activity and provide other website and internet usage-related services for the website operator. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. You can prevent recorded data generated by the cookie concerning your use of the website (including your IP address) from being sent to Google and prevent the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available via the link <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. Additional information on the Terms of Use and Data Privacy Policy of Google Analytics may be found at <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/> and <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

The tables below list the first-party and third-party cookies and identifiers used by Sesam Limited on its website:

**Cookie name** | **Description** | **Validity period** | **Cookie type**  
---|---|---|---  
k | User ID/Auth | 7 days | Alphanumeric  
sid | Session tracking | 24 hours | Alphanumeric  
__cfduid | Cloudflare client identification → performance | 1 year | Alphanumeric  
_ga | Used to distinguish users | 2 years | Alphanumeric  
_gat_UA-xxxxxxxxxx | Used to throttle rate | 1 min | Numeric  
_gid | Used to distinguish users | 24 hours | Alphanumeric  
_odTrck | Tracking of the browsing origin data | 48 hours | Alphanumeric  
_dc_gtm°UA-xxxxxx | Used to distinguish users | 1 min | Numeric  
_uetsid | BING Remarketing tracking SID | 30 mins | Alphanumeric  
  
Some of our pages may also contain web beacons which allow us to collect information on the volume and origin of visitor traffic to our pages as well as general demographic information about these visitors. This data is stored anonymously, it does not contain any personal information and can thus be disclosed to third parties, particularly for information or statistical analysis purposes, particularly in order to analyze the performance of our marketing promotions.

We may also use advertising cookies to collect certain demographics and usage statistics to improve the services. In particular, we use the following Google Analytics Advertising Features: Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting; Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers.

We also make use of “social plugins”, i.e. plugins for social networks, including particularly the Facebook “Share” button. The facebook.com website is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plug-ins usually feature the Facebook logo. Besides Facebook, we use plug-ins by Twitter (provider: Twitter, Inc., 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA), Pinterest (provider: Pinterest Inc., 808 Brannan Street, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA (if you are located in the USA), Pinterest Europe Ltd., Palmerston House, 2nd Floor, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, Ireland (if you are located outside the USA)), Instagram (1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA) and GooglePlus (provider: Google).

For data privacy reasons, we deliberately opted against utilizing direct social network plug-ins on our website. Instead, we employ an alternative technical solution that allows you to decide whether to transmit data to the social network operators and when. Thus when you visit the website, data are never automatically transmitted to social networks such as Facebook or Twitter. Only when you actively click on the respective button yourself will your web browser connect to the servers of the respective social network, i.e. clicking on elements then clicking on the social network’s icon indicates your consent to your browser connecting to the servers of the respective social network and sending usage data to that social network operator, whether or not you are a subscriber of such social network.

We have no influence over the nature or scope of data that social networks may then gather. For information regarding the purpose and scope of data collection, further processing and use of data by social networks and regarding your data privacy rights and relevant configuration settings, see the social networks’ respective data privacy advisories.

## Use of your testimonials

From time to time, we may post customer testimonials on our website. We either use scrambled customer information that does not allow the identification of our customers or, if such testimonials allow the identification of our customers, will obtain your prior consent by e-mail to allow Sesam Limited to use the following information for promotional purposes or for testimonials: first name, surname initial, picture, town/city, country of residence, all or parts of the correspondence e-mails between you and the brand operated by Sesam Limited.

## How do we deal with information from individuals under the locally applicable legal age?

The guardian-angel-reading.com website does not seek to collect personal data from individuals under the locally applicable legal age. Individuals under the locally applicable legal age should receive permission from their parent or legal guardian before providing any personal information to Sesam Limited on the guardian-angel-reading.com website.

## What happens if this privacy policy changes?

Our privacy policy applies to all the information that we process about you. We may occasionally make updates or changes to this privacy policy, which you can consult via a direct link on all pages of the guardian-angel-reading.com website.

These changes and updates apply as of the last update date indicated at the top of this document. We therefore ask you to consult it on a regular basis. However, Sesam Limited commits not to make any changes which might weaken the protection of your personal data without your consent.

## Business Transitions

In the event Sesam Limited goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal data might be among the assets transferred. You will be notified of any such change in ownership or control of your personal data via the contact information you have provided via the website.

## How can you contact us?

If you have any comments or questions about this document, you can contact us at [privacy@guardian-angel-reading.com](mailto:privacy@guardian-angel-reading.com)

Our address in Europe: Sesam Ltd – 8A Pitmans Alley – Main Street – Gibraltar
